import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet1: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Hearing goes without any effort, and it is a/an________ action.",
    "options": [
      "voluntary",
      "involuntary",
      "critical",
      "analytical"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Horizontal communication takes place from ________.",
    "options": [
      "superior to subordinate",
      "subordinate to superior",
      "employees with same status",
      "none of these"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "The way to keep permanent records for business is termed as ________",
    "options": [
      "business letters",
      "ledgers",
      "reviews",
      "reports"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "________ of the letter consists the main message.",
    "options": [
      "Heading",
      "Salutation",
      "Body",
      "Closing"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "A Creative way to brainstorm, plan, and put your vision into action is to use a/an ____",
    "options": [
      "mind map",
      "Visualization",
      "Time log",
      "To-do list"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "A memorandum (memo) is considered a brief form of written communication for ______",
    "options": [
      "internal use",
      "legal",
      "external",
      "formal"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "________ meetings do not follow the conventional rules.",
    "options": [
      "formal",
      "informal",
      "executive",
      "academic"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "________ is one of the major hiring factors.",
    "options": [
      "family background",
      "communication skills",
      "good looks",
      "references"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Dressing sense is the ability to choose clothes that would make us look ______",
    "options": [
      "attractive",
      "repulsive",
      "dominating",
      "fascist"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Naturally, the first step to communicating is ____",
    "options": [
      "listening",
      "speaking",
      "reading",
      "writing"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }
]
